cheekymunkey.co.uk 2008-10-04

# Cheeky Munkey » Privacy

Cheeky Munkey respects the privacy of visitors to the website. This privacy policy is intended to protect an individual's privacy. It explains what type of information we collect from users of the website and what we do with that information. 

Most of the website is freely available to browse without becoming a registered user. For some services or areas on the site, we will ask that you provide us with information about you and/or your company such as name, job title, email address, and other types of information that enable us to provide services and information to you. 

If you order online with us, we may ask you to provide further information, including but not limited to financial information, equipment information, and other personal information. We may collect other personal information when you provide comments or participate in surveys. 

When you visit our site, we collect certain technical and routing information about your computer to facilitate your use of the site. For example, we log environmental variables, such as browser type, operating system and CPU speed, and the Internet Protocol address of your originating Internet Service Provider, to bring you the best possible service. We also record search requests and results to ensure the accuracy and efficiency of our search engine. We use your IP address to track your use of the site. 

The Cheeky Munkey website uses two types of cookies. "Cookies" are small data files, typically made up of a string of text and numbers, which assign you a unique identifier. A "client cookie" is sent to your browser so that our systems remember your requests and keep track of the pages you view on our site and which services you use. A "server cookie" is maintained on our systems to recognize you when you return to the site. This information allows us to better administer the site and provide a more tailored and user-friendly service to you. You may set your browser to notify you when you receive a cookie or to prevent cookies from being sent; if so, you may limit the functionality we can provide you when you visit our site. 

Finally, we collect aggregate information about the use of our site, such as which pages are most frequently visited, how many visitors we receive daily, and how long visitors stay on each page. 

Cheeky Munkey strives to have in place appropriate means to protect your information. However, in providing your information over a public or third party network, you do so at your own risk. 

The information we collect about you in the course of our relationship is used to facilitate your orders or other activities between us, and to provide you with both general and tailored information about offers, products, services or other useful information from us or others. If you order products or services from us, we may maintain an order history for your account. We also may combine information you have provided to us in communications offline with the information you have given us online (or vice versa), to provide a more customized experience for you when you deal with us. We use demographic and site usage information collected from visitors to improve the usefulness of our site and to prepare aggregate, non-identifying, information used in marketing, site advertising, or similar activities. 

As our services evolve, the types of information we collect may change. Please check this policy frequently for the most current explanation of our data practices. 

We do not sell your email address or other identifying information to third parties. We may provide to others the aggregate statistics about our customers' orders or related site activity for purposes of marketing or promotion. 

We may disclose information about you to others if we have a good faith belief that we are required to do so by law or legal process, to respond to claims, or to protect the rights, property or safety of Cheeky Munkey or others. 

Cheeky Munkey maintains customer information, including order history and site usage data, for a length of time appropriate to our business needs. You may contact us to correct or update any personal identifying information, which you have submitted to us, or should you have questions about information maintained by us. If you operate in the European Union or other jurisdictions that provide access rights under law, you may access your personal information or have it corrected or updated in accordance with applicable law by contacting us. In some jurisdictions, you may be charged a reasonable fee for access to information. You can opt out of receiving information about non-Cheeky Munkey activities, products or services and/or opt out of having your data provided to third parties for marketing purposes by contacting us. 

Please feel free to contact us at info@cheekymunkey.co.uk if you have questions or concerns about this privacy policy.
